Guide to the Yale Objects Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Yale objects collection, 1697-2002; Series I
  - #924 Silver loving cup with 2 handles, square base. Engraved "In loving memory/Stephen Bogert Roe... " engraved with names of graduates, circa 1895 (Box 128)
  - #925 Silver loving cup, 2 handles, engraved scene of lake, hills, trees... "Cleveland Alumni Prize Cup" on one side. On other "Won by" and names of winners, circa 1885-90 (Box 128)
  - #926 Pewter stein with glass bottom. Used in the original Mory's period of Mrs. Mory and Eddie Oakley, undated (Box 128)
  - #927 Octagonal silver cup engraved with floral design, one handle. "Class cup 1847 to the eldest child of Wm. A. Gunton from his classmates. Yale College... 1850" (Box 128)
  - #928 Silver goblet stem is carved baby and ivy, cup is engraved: "Presented to Holley Washington McCreary, the 'Class Boy'... by the class of 1865.. .", 1868 (Box 128)
  - #929 Silver goblet with engraving. Stem is carved baby. Cup engraved "Willard Parker. 'Class Boy' June 30th, 1869.", circa 1869 (Box 128)
  - #930 Silver plate engraved "Exedone Honorabilis Gubernatoris Elihu Yale armiger Anno 1687", undated (Box 129)
  - #931 Large oval-shaped tray with raised design, 4 legs, 2 curved handles. Engraved: "White Ambassador" "Berlin 1900" "1853" "To Yale University" "... ", good (Box 390)
  - #932 Black felt mortarboard with gold tassel, size 7 1/4. On inside, initials WSE, undated (Box 130)
  - #933 Black top hat, collapsible, undated (Box 130)
  - #934 Ornamental piece from old exhibit cabinets which were in the "Gutenberg" room, MSS&A. Curved metal with leaf design on top, undated (Box 131)
  - #935 Metal on wood. Plan of lecture room, Yale University Zoological Laboratory, undated (Box 132, Folder 1)
  - #936 Copper plate of Harkness Tower, undated (Box 133, Folder 1)
  - #937 Copper plate--picture of man [affiliated with Yale class of 1953]?, undated (Box 133, Folder 2)
  - #938 Copper plate--picture of man [affiliated with Yale class of 1953]?, undated (Box 133, Folder 3)
  - #939 Copper plate--picture of class of 1876, 55th reunion, 1931 (Box 133, Folder 4)
  - #940 Copper plate--picture of monument to A.J. Hadley, undated (Box 133, Folder 4)
  - #941 A Yale Oarsman, by Mrs. Maude Hutchins. The model was Thomas Early (Y. 1931), undated
  - #942 Model of the Old Campus by F.T. Gilling for the Yale Exhibit at the St. Louis World's Fair, 1904. In glass case, on table
  - #943 Piece of the Yale Fence, undated
  - #944 Piece of the Yale Fence, undated
  - #945 Painting of Brick Row and Yale Fence with students, in large carved gold frame. By A.C. Howland, N.A, undated
  - #946 Tinted drawing of Yale Campus by Richard Rummell. In dark brown wood frame, 1905
  - #947 Rubbing of stone in India commemorating Elihu Yale, when he headed the East India Co. Inscription in Latin. Red printing. Wood frame, undated
  - #948 Wooden top with metal point, circa 1905 (Box 134, Folder 1)
  - #949 SUMMERTERM T-shirt for Yale's summer term, 1975. Designed by Rollin Johnson '77, Rachel Wilder '77, Sonia Senkiwsky '78, 1977 (Box 134, Folder 2)
  - #950 Metal Stickpin with Yale crest, inscribed "Yale University Bicentennial 1701-1901" (Box 134, Folder 6)
  - #951 Tapestry scroll sent by Japanese Yale Alumni greeting the University at Yale's Bicentennial, Oct. 1901. In wooden box (Box 230)
  - #952 Two blue and white "Y" buttons pinned on a blue ribbon, good (Box 134, Folder 3)
  - #953 White ribbon with gold printing "YALE", undated (Box 134, Folder 4)
  - #954 Metal Stickpin with Yale crest, inscribed "Yale University Bicentennial 1701-1901," with blue ribbon (Box 134, Folder 5)
  - #955 Blue "Yale" button with white letters, undated (Box 134, Folder 7)
  - #956 Triangular flag, light brown cloth with blue "Y" sewn on, undated (Box 134, Folder 8)
  - #957 Linen apron, dance souvenir, dance program, 10th annual Calico Hall Ball, New Haven. At the Music Hall, 1870 (Box 134, Folder 9)
  - #958 Blue and white paper banner: "For God, For Country And for the Davies Mansion.", undated (Box 134, Folder 10)
  - #959 Blue Banner: "Yale 1883" (Box 134, Folder 11)
  - #960 Cigarette package premium showing Yale banner, bulldog, seal and cheer, circa 1910 (Box 134, Folder 12)
  - #961 Metal plate of the Yale seal, undated (Box 134, Folder 13)
  - #962 Gateway keys, plaque reads "Original Gate Keys Yale College", circa 1700s (Box 135)
  - #963 Wooden plaque with metal letters. Zeta Psi, undated (Box 136)
  - #964 Fragment of molding from a fireplace in the Samuel Russell house in Branford--mounted on wooden plaque, undated (Box 137)
  - #965 Stone from old Chancel arch of church at Stanton Fitzwarren, Wiltshire, where Rev. John Woodbridge was Rector from 1625 until his death in 1637, undated (Box 138, Folder 1)
  - #966 Piece of Yale Blue fabric from President's gown, undated (Box 138, Folder 2)
  - #967 Wax seal of John Pierpont (Y. 1804) showing his left profile, undated (Box 138, Folder 3)
  - #968 Seal of John Pierpont (Y. 1804) featuring a fox over the initials "JP", undated (Box 138, Folder 4)
  - #969 Set of 3 silks featuring Yale track, football, and crew illustrations, undated (Box 138, Folder 5)
  - #970 Die with Yale shield and banner underneath reading "Lux et Veritas", undated (Box 138, Folder 6)
  - #971 Die with a "Y" as a balance scale; light on one side, surrounded by a wreath, undated (Box 138, Folder 7)
  - #972 Hippocutter Cage, emblem of the the Hippopotamus Club, a luncheon group consisting of Henry Chauncey, Jr, Sidney Lovett, and George Vaill, undated (Box 139)
  - #973 Brochure of various cigar box labels, undated (Box 140, Folder 1)
  - #974 Painting on silk given to Secretary Wilkinson from Japan Association of Private Colleges and Universities on occasion of 8th Overseas Seminar, 1986, undated (Box 140, Folder 2)
  - #975 Velvet lined wooden case fitted for stolen Presidential collar, 1905 (Box 140, Folder 3)
  - #976 Minature baseball bat (Louisville Slugger) with Jim Rice's name signed, undated (Box 141, Folder 1)
  - #977 Medal given to Edward S. Harkness, '97, by the American group of the Societe des Architectes... for service in the advancement of Art and Architecture, 1938 (Box 141, Folder 2)
  - #978 The Junior Fraternity of Zeta Psi requests the pleasure of ______ company at 309 York Street from ___ to ___ o'clock. Dancing invitations, undated (Box 138, Folder 8)
  - #979 Ashtray stamped on bottom "Property of Yale University.", undated (Box 142)
  - #980 Blue cloth banner; used for [Yale Regatta] class championship, 1937 (Box 143, Folder 1)
  - #981 Blue cloth banner; used for [Yale Regatta] class championship, 1938 (Box 143, Folder 2)
  - #982 Blue cloth banner; used for [Yale Regatta] class championship, 1939 (Box 143, Folder 3)
  - #983 Blue cloth banner; used for [Yale Regatta] class championship, 1940 (Box 143, Folder 4)
  - #984 Blue cloth banner; used for [Yale Regatta] class championship, 1941 (Box 143, Folder 5)
  - #985 Blue felt banner with white letters: "1909s" (Box 144, Folder 1)
  - #986 Blue felt banner with white letters: "Yale", undated (Box 144, Folder 2)
  - #987 Blue silk frame with two "Y" pennants and gold decoration, late 1800s (Box 145, Folder 1)
  - #988 Two blue ribbons with Yale insignia, 1892 (Box 145, Folder 2)
  - #989 Phi Beta Kappa gold keys of William (Y. 1920 '26 Ph.D.) and Mabel DeVane('25 Ph.D.)--1st woman elected to Yale Chapter of Phi Beta Kappa, 1920 and 1966 (Box 145, Folder 3)
  - #990 Psi Epsilon plaque owned by James D. Lucey, Yale 1917, circa 1917 (Box 146)
  - #991 Metal scroll and key (Scroll and Key secret society), circa 1907 (Box 147)
  - #992 Delta Kappa; gold, black, and white crescent, inscribed "J.P." and "Yale '72", 1872 (Box 148, Folder 1)
  - #993 Phi Theta Phi fraternity pin inscribed "J.P. Ord Yale '72 [1872]" (Box 148, Folder 2)
  - #994 Two Paper hats. Decorated with cut paper. Stars. Red, white, and blue, undated (Box 148, Folder 3)
  - #995 Book and Bond plaque, Phi Kappa Epsilon, circa 1909 (Box 148, Folder 4)
  - #996 Sterling water pitcher, Examplar Paul Revere 1735-1818, Ensko, New York. "The President and Fellows of Yale University to Thomas Wells Farnam... ", 1942 (Box 149)
  - #997 Silver President's Cup--Yale Charities Drive 1977 BK; 1978 BK, ES; 1980 ES, circa 1977-1980 (Box 149)
  - #998 Urn with 2 ram heads as part of the handles. Inscribed "To William Sloane Coffin on the occasion of his fiftieth birthday April 15, 1929." (Box 150)
  - #999 Urn inscribed "to Yale University from Andrew Dickson White, Class of 1853, Ambassador of the United States of America, Berlin 1899", 1903 (Box 151)
  - #1000 Tureen inscribed "To Yale University 1903 from Andrew Dickson White, Class of 1853, Ambassador of the United States, Berlin 1899", undated (Box 152)
  - #1001 Necktie with "40sY50th" on it. Class of 1940's 50th reunion tie, 1989 (Box 148, Folder 5)
  - #1002 Fraternity paddles (2) from Beta Theta Pi (Phi Chi Chapter), 1909 (Box 153, Folder 1-2)
  - #1003 Black Supreme Court Robe of David J. Brewer, circa 1890's (Box 154)
  - #1004 Blue robe with black trim, undated (Box 155)
  - #1005 Black robe with brocade belonging to A.F. Wright, undated (Box 155)
  - #1006 Red gown with pink trim, Cambridge LL.D. (honorary), 1922 (Box 156)
  - #1007 Crimson robe with red trim, Oxford DCL (Honorary), 1922 (Box 157)
  - #1008 Red robe with blue trim. The first gown of the Yale President, 1937 (Box 157)
  - #1009 Academic hood, unidentified. Black, blue, and white, undated (Box 158)
  - #1010 Academic hood, black and blue, undated (Box 158)
  - #1011 Academic hood, black and blue, undated (Box 158)
  - #1012 Academic hood, black and blue, undated (Box 158)
  - #1013 Academic hood, black, white, and purple, undated (Box 158)
  - #1014 Academic hood--light blue and red from University of Aberdeen LL.D, 1922 (Box 158)
  - #1015 Brick from unknown building: "From (the) Jo... y house. North.... om. Built 1754-1759" (Box 159, Folder 1)
  - #1016 Dark gray brick from unknown building, circa 1700s (Box 159, Folder 2)
  - #1017 Cream brick from unknown building with WORTLEY LEEDS etched in it, circa 1800s (Box 159, Folder 3)
  - #1018 Brick painted red on one side and gold on four sides. "OLD SOUTH," YALE-1893 is painted on one gold side with bright gold paint (Box 159, Folder 4)
  - #1019 Brick with a quarter of it missing. A label on it says Nathaniel Thorpe 1720-1725 (Box 159, Folder 5)
  - #1020 Cross attached to red, white, and blue ribbon. On the cross is the name "New Haven." Attached cardboard states, "W W I medal to 1st Lt. H.D. Hooker.", circa 1916-1918 (Box 160, Folder 1)
  - #1021 Two white clay pipes with red painted at the end of each one's stem. Both are stamped, "Made in England." In a box with a piece of gunny sack, undated (Box 160, Folder 2)
  - #1022 Wooden box stamped: "Yale University, Dies for stamping Beckwith Medal" Discontinued June 1949, circa 1949 (Box 160, Folder 3)
  - #1023 Mustard ceramic jug with a handle. Neck is broken off. ROISDORPER QUELLE MINERAL engraved on it, undated (Box 160, Folder 4)
  - #1024 Wooden spoon with DUM VIVIMUS VIVAMUS engraved on it and a plaque stating: "Junior Promenade Committee.. .", 1933 (Box 317)
  - #1025 Cream drawstring pouches still containing some tobacco. Each pouch has CLASS DAY, YALE and then the year. Years encompass 1932-1942 (Box 160, Folder 5)
  - #1026 Plaque from a French 75 gun on which is inscribed: Presented to the U.S. cruiser Yale by the students and graduates of Yale University May 1898" (Box 160, Folder 7)
  - #1027 Painting on canvas of someone praying in a graveyard. It is signed in the lower left corner by Deane Keller, undated (Box 161)
  - #1028 Deane Keller painting of a galley sailing on a river, undated (Box 162)
  - #1029 Blue banner with gold trim with the "Yale" beast on it, undated (Box 163)
  - #1030 Law School banner: shield with an alligator, a dog, and three other objects with two legs, undated (Box 163)
  - #1031 Old style School of Forestry banner: three trees, acorns on a blue background, gold fringe, undated (Box 163)
  - #1032 Blue bunting, undated (Box 163)
  - #1033 Yale School of Nursing banner: four white inverted triangles on a black background, open book with Hebrew writing, undated (Box 163)
  - #1034 Old style School of Medicine banner: green background, open book with Hebrew writing, on either side of book are two snakes wrapped around two staffs, undated (Box 163)
  - #1035 School of Engineering banners. Red background with criss-crossing white lines, yellow and black across the banner, undated (Box 163)
  - #1036 Old Style School of Art and Architecture banner: greenish cream background and blue and green squares. Two horses on one green square and one on other, undated (Box 163)
  - #1037 Red and blue connected squares on white, undated (Box 163)
  - #1037.1 Yale College banner: upper half has cream background with a red X and 3 black symbols in each triangle formed by the X; lower half has blue background.., undated (Box 163)
  - #1038 Framed wooden Eta Phi plaque, circa 1879-1902 (Box 181)
  - #1039 Yale '96 button. White with ble outer ring and blue numbers, 1896 (Box 164)
  - #1040 Blue with YALE '78 Quindecennial written on it. This is from the class of 1878 (Box 164)
  - #1041 Blue with gold '92 with wooden hanger, 1892 (Box 313)
  - #1043 Psi Upsilon fraternity pins, 1911 (Box 164)
  - #1044 Delta Kappa Epsilon: gold, black, and white diamond, 1909 (Box 164)
  - #1045 Academic hood with red, white, and yellow stripes and blue velvet under material, undated (Box 164)
  - #1046 Embroidered pillow. Yale blue satin and white embroidery of the Yale College seal sewn by Sarah Belle Parkhurst, 1900 (Box 165)
  - #1047 Blue necktie with white pigs and yellow letters "YCP" which stands for "Yale Chauvinist Pig." Mock protest against coeducation, 1978 (Box 166, Folder 1)
  - #1048 Jacket pocket type patch, 1915 Lux et Veritas, circa 1980 (Box 166, Folder 2)
  - #1049 Wooden table with octagonal top, center post with three legs, undated
  - #1050 Distinguished service award. "For Service to Yale. Lux et Veritas." On back "Mary B. Griswold, 1981." (Box 166, Folder 3)
  - #1051 Red, white, and blue with 7 stars. Commission pennant of the Thomas S. Gates (CG 51). Flown throughout Desert Shield and the beginning of the Gulf War, 1990-1991 (Box 167)
  - #1052 Union Jack of the USS Thomas S. Gates (CG 51). Used in Desert Shield/Storm in Saudi Arabia, Egypt, and Israel, 1990-1991 (Box 167)
  - #1053 Orange Bravo Flag. Flown during hazardous operations. Used aboard USS Thomas S. Gates (CG 51) during Operation Desert Shield/Storm, 1990-1991 (Box 167)
  - #1054 Gold and blue Kilo flag. Flown to indicate "men working aloft." Used aboard the USS Thomas S. Gates (CG 51) during Desert Shield/Storm, 1990-1991 (Box 167)
  - #1055 Hotel Flag. Used during helicopter/flight operations. Used aboard the USS Thomas S. Gates (CG 51) during Desert Shield/Storm, 1990-1991 (Box 167)
  - #1056 U.S. National Ensign. Used aboard the USS Thomas S. Gates (CG 51) during Desert Shield/Storm during the first week of the war in the Red Sea off S.Arabia, 1991 (Box 167)
  - #1057 One large blue flag with "YALE" in white, circa early 1900s (Box 167)
  - #1058 Charm of a monk belonging to George E. Heisen, 1925s (Box 168, Folder 1)
  - #1059 Charm with Shield shape with a gray horned type head and the word HOUNDS, circa 1925 (Box 168, Folder 1)
  - #1060 Academic gown of President Kingman Brewster. Gray, purple, and black. Has a crown on each lapel, circa 1970s (Box 168)
  - #1061 Round horse-shoe shape signature wheel for William Ressen, 29373
  - #1062 Round horse-shoe shape signature wheel for Henry Chauncey, 29221
  - #1063 Round horse-shoe shape signature wheel for Wilkinson
  - #1064 Yale Alumni Fund Seal and inscription. Re: Centennial Celebration, 1990 (Box 169, Folder 1)
  - #1065 Necktie with Yale Alumni Fund symbol on it made for the Centennial Celebration, 33187
  - #1066 T-shirt with Boyton cartoon. "Lux et Veritas et Pecunia" Yale Alumni Fund, 1990 (Box 169, Folder 3)
  - #1067 Wooden cane, copper bottom and silver top. Inscribed on silver "APB Yale College Class of 1847." Belonged to Abel P. Bull (Box 226)
  - #1068 Small Frisbee for the 20th reunion of the Whiffenpoofs of 1970, 1990 (Box 169, Folder 4)
  - #1069 Framed sign: "The Chapel Service has Begun. Late comers are requested to enter by the... ", undated (Box 169, Folder 5)
  - #1070 Gold key; on the back "Yale University 06s... ", 1906 (Box 169, Folder 6)
  - #1071 Gold colored bulldog stickpin, circa/ 1906 (Box 169, Folder 7)
  - #1072 Blue and white pin. "SIGILL: COLL: YALEN: NOV: PORT: NOV: ANGL. Lux et Veritas", 1906 (Box 169, Folder 8)
  - #1073 Blue and white charm. SIGILL: COLL: YALEN: NOV: POET: NOV: ANGL: Lux et Veritas, 1906 (Box 169, Folder 9)
  - #1074 Leather band with buckle. Ring with "Y.M.C.A. 177" at one end, tag with "Yale 1906s" on the other end (Box 169, Folder 10)
  - #1075 Painting with gold frame--pastoral scene, circa 1900 (Box 216)
  - #1075.1 Handmade beaded fob. Blue background-white Y '06 Made by Mrs. W. Leroy Ulrich, 1906 (Box 169, Folder 11)
  - #1076 Yale University Bicentennial, 1801-1901 medal with a with bow and stick pin (Box 169, Folder 12)
  - #1077 Inscription "VRBS ROMA CVLTOR... ", 1893 (Box 169, Folder 13)
  - #1078 Inscription "PRO SINGULARI ERGA... " Frank E. Brown, Trustee 1954-63, circa 1976 (Box 169, Folder 14)
  - #1079 Inscription "Frank E. Brown, Rome 1980" (Box 169, Folder 15)
  - #1080 Examination table, octagonal, undated
  - #1081 Yale bulldog, "Operation Watchdog"; blue "Save the Cross Campus"; red and white "I am a nuclear war misfit, Spiro", undated (Box 169, Folder 16)
  - #1082 Painted on linen--Yale stein, tobacco pouch and pipe with inscription, circa late 1800s (Box 169, Folder 17)
  - #1083 Samuel French Award: "Presented to Yale University for Excellence in Instruction in Playwriting.. .", 1962 (Box 169, Folder 18)
  - #1084 Samuel French Award: "Presented to Yale University for Excellence in Instruction in Playwriting.. .", 1963 (Box 169, Folder 19)
  - #1085 Sterling silver teaspoon with "Osborn Hall, Yale," etched in the bowl and "C 1898" on the handle back (Box 169, Folder 20)
  - #1086 Board game with tokens, cards, dice, play money, deeds. Everything Yale-oriented. Derivation of board game Monopoly, 1991 (Box 170)
  - #1087 Gold mourning ring. Crystal stone in the shape of a coffin with a picture of a skeleton in it. Around the Ring--gold on black "T. CLAP/OB:IEN:7... ", 1767 (Box 171, Folder 1)
  - #1088 Cut glass cylindrical bottle with sterling top "crowned" by Yale seal. Engraved with "'88' German 1898.", circa 1898 (Box 171, Folder 2)
  - #1089 Original nail from Pierpont house, New Haven's oldest building on original site, undated (Box 171, Folder 3)
  - #1090 Pin with Yale seal, undated (Box 171, Folder 4)
  - #1091 Pin from the Waite Chapter of Phi Delta Phi Law School Society, 1908 Phi Delta; gold and black (Box 171, Folder 5)
  - #1092 Yale class day pipe (2), undated (Box 175)
  - #1093 Miniature sculling oar, circa 1891 (Box 175)
  - #1094 Gold charm rugby pin awarded to L.E. Wales, Jr, 1895 (Box 171, Folder 6)
  - #1095 Gold society pin inscribed "June 9th 1893" Probably belonged to Joseph P. Wales, 1894s (Box 171, Folder 7)
  - #1096 Silver clip pin, Yale Junior Prom Spoon, 1953 (Box 171, Folder 8)
  - #1097 Silver spoon pin with Yale seal, undated (Box 171, Folder 9)
  - #1098 Gold charm, Yale Glee Club inscribed "W. Craven '54." Title and music of "'Neath the Elms.", 1954 (Box 171, Folder 10)
  - #1099 Silver cufflinks with Yale seal, undated (Box 171, Folder 11)
  - #1100 Commemorative long-sleeve T-shirt of Yale Corinthian Yacht Club's Snow and Satisfaction Regatta, 1986 (Box 175)
  - #1101 Commencement hat (mortarboard) commemorating the tenure of David Pease as Dean of the Art School. Clock with 13 numerals in orange on top, 1996 (Box 175)
  - #1102 Nameplate belonging to General Winfield Scott Hancock. Inscribed "General Hancock", circa 1870 (Box 171, Folder 12)
  - #1103 Gold Phi Beta Kappa Key with Triangle inscribed "Chi Delta Theta 1824," and "George C. Murray", 1845 (Box 171, Folder 13)
  - #1104 Gold and Enamel Yale pin, heart shaped, circa 1909 (Box 171, Folder 14)
  - #1105 Silver spoon with engraving of the Yale Boat House in bowl and "Yale" in blue on the handle, undated (Box 171, Folder 15)
  - #1106 Blue, gold and white Yale insignia pin, undated (Box 171, Folder 16)
  - #1107 Flower-like pin with "Y'87" printed on it and worn by a member of the prom committee, 1887. Blue and red ribbons attached (Box 171, Folder 17)
  - #1108 Two empty wine bottles, chardonnay and pinot noir. Label: "150 Years of Rowing, Y. 1845-1993." Served at the anniversary banquet (Box 176)
  - #1126 Blue flag bearing Yale class years of five Goodrich family members, circa 1950 (Box 178, Folder 1)
  - #1127 Yale Loving Cup Class of 1897, circa 1930-1952 (Box 179)
  - #1128 Framed plaque commemorating the groundbreaking for the Dept. of Molecular Biophysics & Biochemistry Center for Structural Biology, 1990 (Box 182)
  - #1129 Watercolor painting of football pileup with referee scratching head as if asking, "What do I do?", by A. Taylor (sp?), 1948 (Box 302)
  - #1130 Black and white watercolor titled, "Evening at Mory's", by Orson Lowell, undated (Box 302)
  - #1131 Carved wooden head from the Old Library. Described as a "native American Indian", 1846 (Box 184)
  - #1132 Carved wooden head from the Old Library. Described as a "lion", 1846 (Box 185)
  - #1133 Carved wooden head from the Old Library. Described as a "man with flowing hair", 1846 (Box 186)
  - #1134 Carved wooden head from the Old Library. Described as a "man with a toothache", 1846 (Box 187)
  - #1135 Blue felt banner with white letters: "YALE 1925", undated (Box 188)
  - #1136 Small pin with block "Y" and "Engineering Inspection trip 1925, undated (Box 188)
  - #1137 Blue Wedgwood plates (6) with Yale scenes, 1949 (Box 189)
  - #1138 Engraving plate, Yale song, "Old Yale" and prints from the plate, circa 1902 (Box 188)
  - #1139 Emroidery of the Yale seal, circa 1910 (Box 188)
  - #1140 Pair of work boots found behind interior wall of Sterling Memorial Library with three pages of December 1928 magazine, circa 1929 (Box 190)
  - #1141 Image of a Yale hammer thrower, circa 1930's (Box 192, Folder 1)
  - #1142 Brick from old South College, circa 1793 (Box 191)
  - #1143 Dr. Cushing's opera hat, circa 1920 (Box 194)
  - #1144 Painted windowpane from Sterling Memorial Library. "Negro eating watermelon" is the depicted scene, circa 1930 (Box 195)
  - #1145 Broken painted windowpane from Sterling Memorial Library, circa 1930 (Box 195)
  - #1146 Framed and signed print of an etching of Harkness Tower by Luigi Kasimir, circa 1929 (Box 235)
  - #1147 Beta Theta Pi fraternity plaque, circa 1930-1950 (Box 198)
  - #1148 Beta Theta Pi chapter fraternity plaque, circa 1930-1950 (Box 198)
  - #1149 Beta Theta Pi fraternity plaque, circa 1930-1950 (Box 198)
  - #1150 Beta Theta Pi fraternity plaque, circa 1930-1950 (Box 198)
  - #1151 Pencil drawing of A. B. Giamatti by Jeffrey C. Collins, Y. 1985, circa 1985
  - #1152 Wooden megaphone with "Y" on side, circa 1920
  - #1153 Blue felt banner with white letters "YALE 1921", undated (Box 199)
  - #1154 White cotton hat with centered blue letters "Y 21"; some water stains, undated (Box 199)
  - #1155 Original painting by Milton Clow, undated (Box 200)
  - #1156 Connecticut Hall door with inlaid photographs from the late nineteenth century, circa 1790
  - #1157 Commemorative tobacco pouch, inscribed "Class Day Yale 1919" (Box 192, Folder 2)
  - #1158 Sweater of Giles P. Greene, circa 1911 (Box 202)
  - #1159 Portrait of "Jerry the Newsboy", circa 1990 (Box 201)